A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 3, Series 15 FA1485
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants and Program Files, 1982-2012; 1
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) - Administration and Budget (Box 436, Folder 7)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) (Box 437, Folder 1-5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) (Box 438, Folder 1-2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020694) - Proposal Development (Box 438, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Administration and Budget (Box 438, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Proposal Development (Box 438, Folder 5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Correspondence (Box 438, Folder 6)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Articles and Background (Box 438, Folder 7)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Grant Products (Box 439, Folder 1-3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Darmouth College - Olson (20031304) - Background (Box 439, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000252) - Measuring the Quality of Health Services for Young Children - Correspondence (Box 440, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000252) - Measuring the Quality of Health Services for Young Children - Administration and Budget (Box 440, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000252) - Measuring the Quality of Health Services for Young Children - Grant Products (Box 440, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000252) - Measuring the Quality of Health Services for Young Children - Proposal Development (Box 440, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Grant Products (Box 440, Folder 5-6)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Correspondence (Box 441, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Proposal Development (Box 441, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Somers (20020487) - Grant Products (Box 441, Folder 3-5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Budget and Administration (Box 442, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Correspondence (Box 442, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Center for Health Care Strategies - Brodsky (20020487) - Articles and Background (Box 442, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - NICHQ - Homer-Margolis (20010362) (Box 442, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - NICHQ - Homer-Margolis (20010362) - Proposal Development (Box 443, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20010389) - Supporting National Efforts to Improve Child Health and Development Services, Phase II - Proposal Development (Box 443, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20010389) - Supporting National Efforts to Improve Child Health and Development Services, Phase II - Grant Products (Box 443, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20010389) - Supporting National Efforts to Improve Child Health and Development Services, Phase II - Correspondence (Box 443, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20010389) - Supporting National Efforts to Improve Child Health and Development Services, Phase II - Budget and Administration (Box 443, Folder 5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20010583) - Proposal (Box 444, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20010583) - Administration and Budget (Box 444, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20010583) - Correspondence (Box 444, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20010583) - Grant Products (Box 444, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Grant Products (Box 444, Folder 5-6)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Grant Products (Box 445, Folder 1-4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Budget and Adminisration (Box 446, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Articles and Background (Box 446, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Correspondence (Box 446, Folder 3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20000512) - Understanding Medicaid Parents' Concerns with the Health Care System - Proposal Development (Box 446, Folder 4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Columbia University - Foster (20010200), 2000-2001 (Box 447, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center - Ngo-Metzger (20020110) (Box 447, Folder 2)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - FACCT, Inc. - Bethell (20020111) (Box 447, Folder 3-4)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - National Academy of Sciences - Pellmar (20020366) (Box 447, Folder 5)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - National Academy of Sciences - Pellmar (20020366) (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Society of General Internal Medicine (SGIM) - Bigby (20020825), 2002-2003 (Box 448, Folder 2-3)
  - Child Development and Preventive Care - Society of General Internal Medicine (SGIM) - Bigby (20020825) - Commissioned Papers (Box 448, Folder 4-5)
  - Johns Hopkins University - Grason (20040369), 2003-2005 (Box 449, Folder 1)
  - University of Michigan - Markel (20030391) (Box 449, Folder 2-3)
  - University of Colorado Hospital Authority - Ross (20010374), 2000-2006 (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - University of Colorado Hospital Authority - Ross (20010374) - Grant Products (Box 450, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Colorado Hospital Authority - Ross (20010374) - Proposal Development (Box 450, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Colorado Hospital Authority - Ross (20010374) - Articles and Background (Box 451, Folder 1-2)
  - Benefits 2001-2002 (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - Benefits 2002-2003 (Box 451, Folder 4)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2, 2002-2004 (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2 - Grant Products (Box 451, Folder 6)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2 - Correspondence (Box 451, Folder 7)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2 - Administration and Budget (Box 451, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2 - Proposal Development (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers University - Crystal (20020440) - Experience of State PAPs: Lessons for Design of a National Benefit, Phase 2 - Grant Products (Box 452, Folder 2-3)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA) - Ward (20010413), 2001-2002 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA) - Ward (20010413) - Proposal Development (Box 452, Folder 5)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA) - Ward (20010413) - Administration and Budget (Box 452, Folder 6)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA) - Ward (20010413) - Correspondence (Box 452, Folder 7)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA) - Ward (20010413) - Grant Products (Box 453, Folder 1-4)
  - The Forest Park Trust - Scalia (20020682), 2002-2004 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - Primary Care Development Corp. - Chin (20010002), 2000-2001 (Box 453, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, IOM - Hurtado (20010197), 2000-2001 (Box 454, Folder 1)
  - Conservancy of Historic Battery Park - Price, 2001-2004 (Box 454, Folder 2)
  - Phipps Community Development Corp. (20020868) (Box 454, Folder 3)
  - Community Environmental Center - Cramer (20020808), 2002-2004 (Box 454, Folder 4)
  - New York City Tree Consortium - Bernardo (20030123), 2002-2003 (Box 454, Folder 5)
  - Greenbelt Conservancy - Toth (20030265), 2002-2004 (Box 454, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University - Parikh (20030365), 2003-2005 (Box 454, Folder 7)
  - City Parks Foundation - Crumlish (20030574), 2003-2004 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - Horticultural Society of New York - Ito (20031307), 2003-2004 (Box 455, Folder 2)
  - Phipps Community Development Corp. - Henriquez (20030789), 2003-2004 (Box 455, Folder 3)
  - Asphalt Green - Harris (20030787), 2003-2004 (Box 455, Folder 4)
  - AcademyHealth - Helms (20040625), 2004-2006 (Box 455, Folder 5)
  - Georgia State University Research Foundation - Minyard (20020767) (Box 455, Folder 6)
  - Harris Interactive - Zapert (20030124) - 2002 Grantee Survey, 2002-2003 (Box 455, Folder 7)
  - Primary Care Development Corp. - Kotelchuck (20090606) (Box 455, Folder 8)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Boufford (20090605) (Box 455, Folder 9)
  - Greater New York Hospital Association - Johnson (20090146) (Box 455, Folder 10)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Rivero (20050670), 2005-2006 (Box 455, Folder 11)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Palfreman (20070749), 2007-2008 (Box 455, Folder 12)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Rivero (20040419), 2003-2004 (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - Velar Studios - Gregor (20100077), 2009 (Box 456, Folder 2)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York - Tallon (20090145) (Box 456, Folder 3)
  - United Hospital Fund - Tallon (20070185) (Box 456, Folder 4)
  - Teachers College Columbia University - Brosnan (20060285), 2006-2007 (Box 456, Folder 5)
  - University of St. Thomas - Durenburger (20080238) (Box 456, Folder 6)
  - Harris Interactive - Zapert (20060647) (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Public Views 2006 (Box 456, Folder 8)
  - 2008 Public Views (Box 456, Folder 9)
  - 2008 Public Views Report (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Public Views 2008 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Jacobs Institute of Women's Health - Romans (980552), 1996-2001 (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Covance Health Economics and Outcome - Steinberg (990203), 1998-2001 (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University - Carrino (990558), 1999-2003 (Box 457, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Coalition - Koval (20030195), 2002-2003 (Box 458, Folder 1)
  - Publicolor, Inc. - Shuman (20020179), 1999-2004 (Box 458, Folder 2)
  - City Parks Foundation - Rivel (20020243), 2001-2003 (Box 458, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Botanic Garden - Kirby (20020296), 2001-2003 (Box 458, Folder 4)
  - Trust for Public Land - Harvey (20020295) (Box 458, Folder 5)
  - New York Botanical Garden - Long (20020269) (Box 458, Folder 6)
  - New York University (NYU) - Greene (20020566), 2002-2003 (Box 459, Folder 1)
  - Medscape - DesLauriers (20040769), 2004-2005 (Box 459, Folder 2)
  - Mathew Greenwald Associates - Elmlinger (20060071), 2005-2009 (Box 459, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Griner (20080232), 2008-2009 (Box 459, Folder 4)
  - International Society for Quality in Health Care - Boland (20090440) (Box 459, Folder 5)
  - Independent Sector - Aviv (20090445) (Box 459, Folder 6)
  - Health Services Research Association of Australia and New Zealand - Hall (20070359) (Box 459, Folder 7)
  - Health Services Research Association of Australia and New Zealand - Hall (20060491) (Box 459, Folder 8)
  - Health Services Research Association of Australia and New Zealand - Hall (20050432) (Box 459, Folder 9)
  - Health Services Research Association of Australia and New Zealand - Cumming (20090444), 2009-2010 (Box 459, Folder 10)
  - Health Services Research Association of Australia and New Zealand - Cumming (20080194), 2008-2009 (Box 459, Folder 11)
  - Health Care for All (MA) - McDonough (20080289) (Box 459, Folder 12)
  - Harvard University - Shumaker (20080081), 2007 (Box 459, Folder 13)
  - Harris Interactive - Zapert (20040762) (Box 459, Folder 14)
  - Harris Interactive - Zapert (20040704) (Box 459, Folder 15)
  - Harris Interactive (20030376) - 2003 Communications Survey (Box 460, Folder 1)
  - Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - Crystal (20080226), 2008-2009 (Box 460, Folder 2)
  - Grantmakers in Health - LeRoy (20090443) (Box 460, Folder 3)
  - Grantmakers in Aging - Farquhar, 2009 (Box 460, Folder 4)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - McGencey (20090441) (Box 460, Folder 5)
  - Foundation Center - Smith (20090440) (Box 460, Folder 6)
  - The Educational Broadcasting Co, - Heffner (20020170), 2001-2002 (Box 460, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20080388) - International Symposium on Health Care Policy Fall 2009 (Box 460, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20070536) - 2008 International Symposium, 2008-2009 (Box 460, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20060581) - 2007 International Symposium, 2006-2008 (Box 460, Folder 10)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20050595) - 2006 International Symposium, 2005-2006 (Box 461, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20040503) - 2005-2006 Harkness Fellowships Authorization, 2004-2006 (Box 461, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20020536) - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellowships Authorization, 2002-2004 (Box 461, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth Fund (20000711) - 2001 International Symposium, 2000-2001 (Box 461, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (20030514) - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellowships Authorization, 2003-2005 (Box 461, Folder 5)
  - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellowships Authorization (20000577), 2000-2002 (Box 461, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Landes (20080134) - 2009 Audience Survey, 2008-2009 (Box 461, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University - Kearney (20090688) - 2009 Columbia Journalism Review Insert (Box 461, Folder 8)
  - Columbia University - Kearney (20080132) - 2008 Columbia Journalism Review Insert (Box 461, Folder 9)
- Declinations and Project Authorizations, 1934-2011; 2
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 38, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 41, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 42, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2003 July-2004 June (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Project Payments, 2003 July-September, 2003 July-October (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Project Payments, 2003 October-December, 2003 October-2004 January (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Project Payments, 2004 January-March, 2004 January-April (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Project Payments, 2004 April-June, 2004 April-July (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Project Letters, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 76, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 78, Folder 2-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 79, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-L, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 81, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 82, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Z, 2004 July-2005 June (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 143, Folder 3-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - A-D, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 144, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - A-D, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 145, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - A-D, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - E-N, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 146, Folder 2-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - E-N, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 147, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - E-N, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 148, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - E-N, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 149, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - N-Z, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - N-Z, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 150, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - N-Z, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 151, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs - N-Z, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 152, Folder 2-5)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 153, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Turn-Downs, 2001 July-2002 June (Box 154, Folder 1-2)
  - Project Letters, 2001 July-November (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Project Letters, 2001 November-2002 February, 2001 November-2002 March (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Project Letters, 2002 March-June, 2002 March-July (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-H, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 155, Folder 2-3)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-H, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 156, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-H, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 157, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-H, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 158, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - I-T, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 158, Folder 4-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - I-T, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 159, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - I-T, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 160, Folder 1-5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - I-T, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 161, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - U-Z and Miscellaneous, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 162, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - U-Z and Miscellaneous, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 163, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - U-Z and Miscellaneous, 2002 July-2003 June (Box 164, Folder 1-2)
  - Project Letters, 2002 July-October, 2002 July-November (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Project Letters, 2002 November-2003 Februrary, 2002 November-2003 March (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Project Letters, 2003 March-June, 2003 March-July (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2000 July-2001 March (Box 188, Folder 2-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2000 July-2001 March (Box 189, Folder 1-4)
  - Project Letters, 2000 July-2001 June (Box 190, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-C, 1999 June-2001 May (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-C, 1999 June-2001 May (Box 191, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-C, 1999 June-2001 May (Box 192, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - A-C, 1999 June-2001 May (Box 193, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - D-L, 2000 July-2001 May (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - D-L, 2000 July-2001 May (Box 194, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - D-L, 2000 July-2001 May (Box 195, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - D-L, 2000 July-2001 May (Box 196, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - D-L, 2000 July-2001 May (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Q, 2000 September-2001 May (Box 197, Folder 2-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Q, 2000 September-2001 May (Box 198, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Q, 2000 September-2001 May (Box 199, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - M-Q, 2000 September-2001 May (Box 200, Folder 1-2)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - R-Z, 2000 September-2001 June (Box 200, Folder 3-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - R-Z, 2000 September-2001 June (Box 201, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - R-Z, 2000 September-2001 June (Box 201, Folder 1-4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs - R-Z, 2000 September-2001 June (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Individual Turn-Downs, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 1-4)
  - Declinations - Organizations - A, FY2006-2007 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Declinations - Organizations - B, FY2006-2007 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Declinations - Organizations - C, FY2006-2007 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Declinations - Organizations - C, FY2006-2007 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - Organizations - D, FY2006-2007 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Individual and International Declinations, FY2006-2007 (Box 268, Folder 3-5)
  - Individual and International Declinations, FY2006-2007 (Box 269, Folder 1-3)
  - Declinations - Organizations - E, FY2006-2007 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Declinations - Organizations - F, FY2006-2007 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Declinations - Organizations - G-M, FY2006-2007 (Box 270, Folder 1-6)
  - Declinations - Organizations - N-T, FY2006-2007 (Box 271, Folder 1-6)
  - Declinations - Organizations - U-Y, FY2006-2007 (Box 272, Folder 1-5)
  - Declinations - International Turn-Downs, 2007 July-December (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - Declinations - International Turn-Downs, 2008 January-June (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - Individual Turn-Downs, 2007-2008 (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Declinations - Declined at April 2008 Board Proposal Review Meeting, 2008 April (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Declinations - Declined at July 2008 Board Proposal Review Meeting, 2008 July (Box 340, Folder 1-2)
  - Declinations - A-B, 2007 July-2008 June (Box 340, Folder 3-4)
  - Declinations - C-H, 2007 July-2008 June (Box 341, Folder 1-6)
  - Declinations - I-P, 2007 July-2008 June (Box 342, Folder 1-8)
  - Declinations - Q-Y, 2007 July-2008 June (Box 343, Folder 1-8)
  - Declinations - A, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 343, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - B-I, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 344, Folder 1-8)
  - Declinations - J-M, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 345, Folder 1-4)
  - Declinations - N-R, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 362, Folder 5-9)
  - Declinations - S-Y, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 363, Folder 1-6)
  - Declinations - Declined at November 2008 Board Proposal Review Meeting, 2008 November (Box 363, Folder 7)
  - Declinations - Declined at July 2009 Board Proposal Review Meeting, 2009 July (Box 363, Folder 8)
  - Declinations - Declined at April 2009 Board Proposal Review Meeting, 2009 April (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - Business Turndowns, 2008-2009 (Box 364, Folder 2)
  - International Turndowns, 2008-2009 (Box 364, Folder 3-4)
  - Individual Turndowns, 2008 July-2009 June (Box 365, Folder 1)
  - Declinations - A-B, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 389, Folder 8-9)
  - Declinations - C-K, 2009 July-2010 June (Box 390, Folder 1-9)